SHARIBH AHAMED

□ ahamedsharibh@gmail.com □ 9958015173 □ LUCKNOW

SUMMARY

Sales-motivated Stock Broker, skilled maintaining outstanding client satisfaction by providing customers with regular and informative investment opportunities. Financially-aware professional possesses exceptional skills in research, reporting and customer service. Familiar with financial risk management and economic market trends. Trustworthy and analytically-minded individual with eye for detail and opportunity.

SKILLS

Retail operations Customer flow controlling

Research ability Marketing savvy Communication flower



EXPERIENCE

CUSTOMER RELATIONSHIP EXECUTIVE

TECH MAHINDRA Jul 2017 - Jan 2018

- 1. To handle the queries of customer regarding gst
- 2. To give the resolution about their queries
- 3. filing returns, advice about the tax
- 4. To follow up the customer after resolution
- 5.Guaranteed first-class customer service, 6.enthusiastically anticipating and catering to customer needs and requirements.
- 7. Approached customer interactions in enthusiastic, flexible manner to ensure customer satisfaction.
- 8. Addressed customer service enquiries quickly and accurately.

TRAVEL ADVISOR

JOURNEY SHAPERS Feb 2018 - Oct 2020

Closely monitored team performance, identifying improvements and providing extra training to underachievers.

Proactively monitored employee and customer feedback to identify ways of improving operations and increase profits.

Dealt with complex and difficult customer complaints calmly and professionally, providing effective solutions for continued customer satisfaction.

Planned and coordinated all travel for clients based on budgets, departure times and travel needs.

Organised all holiday matters from beginning to end, including booking tickets and accommodation and securing rental transportation.

Developed travel itineraries for clients based on budgets and client needs.

Conducted in-depth client consultations to develop an understanding of client vision and travel needs.

PROJECTS

TRADING

TRADER Sep 2021 - Present **OPTION TRADER**

SWING TRADER
CURRENCY TRADER
LONG HOLD INVESTOR

EDUCATION

BCOM

CSJM UNIVERSITY Apr 2012 - May 2015

COMPANY SECRETARY

ICSI

CS EXECUTIVE PASSED

NISM

CAPITAL AND SECURITY MARKET Aug 2022 - Aug 2022

NISM 8

NISM 7

NISM SERIES 1

LANGUAGES

english • • • • hindi • • • •